Iván Olivares

Web Developer

+569 8729 8426 ivanolivares98@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/ivanolivareso/

Santiago de Chile, Chile.

Web Developer with 1 year of experience in development, design and deployment of web applications. Collaborated with crossed-functional IT teams to conceptualize and implement a continuous development in cutting-edge web applications. My career has been defined by my commitment to work as a team-player and bring my knowledge to the team.

Experience

Web Developer

Samtech S.A.

03/2023 - 06/2023 Santiago de Chile, Chile

- Development of various functionalities in 5 different projects.
- Applying design with MUI in 5 different projects.
- Creating new components to apply them later on different projects.
- Fixing bugs and working closely with the QA Analyst to correct them.
- Work to achieve a balance between functionality and design.
- Applying accessibility and usability.

Web Developer

MacroActiva SpA.

03/2022 - 06/2022 Santiago de Chile, Chile (Remotely)

- Collaborated with the dev-team to create some of the functionalities using Python, DJANGO, Bootstrap and CSS.
- Helped creating some parts of the back-end server.
- Created forms modules.

Web Developer

iVaras – Duoc ŪC

06/2022 - 09/2022 Santiago de Chile, Chile (Remotely)

- Setting a new project using Django Python.
- Collaborated with the dev-team to implement requirements and applying responsiveness.

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering

Duoc UC - Viña del Mar, Chile

03/2018 - 06/2022

Skills

Programming

JavaScript/Typescript: React - NodeJS - Express - Axios - Material UI - ReactQuery - Angular

Python: Django - Django ORM - Pandas - NumPy

SQL/NoSQL: MSSQL Server - PostgreSQL - Oracle Database - MongoDB

Languages

Spanish - Native Speaker

English - B1